Today, I'm going to show you how to make a cow's water wash costume.
In this process, I will show you how to change from a simple basic shirt to a jacket in the picture.
Then, I will show you how to change from a simple basic shirt to a jacket in the picture.
Next, you can open the CLO app.
If you have downloaded the material, you can upload it to the picture.
I will upload it here.
I have already downloaded it in advance.
You can reply to the public number of this material.
You can download it by replying to the cow's water wash.
Then, after opening our material, we first import a basic style shirt file.
First, let's change it.
We can see that the style to be changed is...
First of all, there is a single plate at the bottom.
Then, the door is relatively wider.
Then, the upper body and the front body are cut up and down.
Then, there are also two vertical cuts on the lower half.
And there is a design of the pocket and the belt cover.
Next, let's change the style.
First, let's see the 3D window.
Its length is still more suitable overall.
So, if we want to add a new plate to the bottom, we can make the shirt shorter.
Here, I am using the edit plate tool.
Go directly to the frame to select the bottom line of the front and back of the front and back of the plate.
Move the whole thing up and down.
Then, I move up.
Then, in the process of moving, you can press the mouse key.
You can press the right mouse button.
It will pop up a window with a moving distance.
Here, we can enter 55.
You can control its length by yourself.
After the change, I will measure the total length of its bottom.
Now, I am using the edit plate tool.
The shortcut key is Z.
The edit plate tool.
I have selected the bottom half of all the lines at once.
Then, at this time, we can see that the total length of the selected line is 638.2.
In this way, the bottom half of the plate is 638.2.
Then, let's draw the plate again.
Use a shape tool.
Find the shape tool on the right.
Or use its shortcut key S.
The shape tool can be directly in the blank area.
Let's go to the 2D window.
In the blank area, press the button.
Enter 638.2.
If the length you change is different from mine.
Or the method is different.
The length may be different from mine.
You can measure it according to my method.
Then, use the edit plate tool to align this plate.
In this way, we get the bottom plate.
Then, let's sew.
You can use free sewing or line sewing.
You can sew the bottom and the front and back of this circle.
And don't miss the door.
Here, I sewed half.
Then, the other half is symmetrical.
After sewing, let's go to the 3D window.
See the 3D window.
Use this adjustment plate tool.
You can move the plate a little bit.
The 3D window.
Right click on this plate.
Add to the side.
Like this.
It will be moved directly to the area near our sewing plate.
Then, just simulate it.
Okay.
After adding this plate.
There should be a button and a buttonhole on the bottom plate.
It's a set of buttons.
We can refer to the position of the door frame above.
Add it to the plate on the bottom plate.
Then, we can first select this line with the edit plate tool.
Its center.
Its door frame should be the middle point.
The left side is half.
It's 20.
So, if we add a button below.
It should also be 20 from the edge.
Right?
Then, if we add a button next.
We first find the button tool.
Find this button tool in the 3D tool bar on our left side.
Found it.
Then, on the plate.
Right-click.
Add the left button directly.
It will pop up such a movable window.
You can see that we can set this button.
The distance between the top and bottom of the plate.
Then, according to the measurement just now.
The left side should be 20.
The top should be 55 divided by 2.
Because it's my plate height divided by 2.
That is 27.5.
Then, next.
I changed the tool to the select the movable button tool.
Because in fact.
We now add this side.
It should be.
You can also see it in the 3D window.
It should be an eye on the surface.
So, I can choose this button.
Right-click.
Turn it into an eye.
Then, right-click again.
Because it is a symmetrical plate.
You can directly copy the corresponding button to the symmetrical modified plate.
Then, we copy it over.
Then, all of this is added.
We will use the button tool below.
Put them together.
Click the button.
Click the eye again.
In this way.
There will be a small lock in 3D.
They are the relationship of gathering.
Okay.
In this way.
We have adjusted this part of the bottom plate.
Then, next.
We will see the part of the door frame.
You can change this door frame first.
Because it is narrower now.
If you want to make it wider.
We can first put it.
Combine the door frame division line with it.
Then, go back to draw a wider division line.
We use the editor tool here.
The shortcut key is Z.
Select the division line together.
The I-Shift key is selected together.
Then, merge.
Then, now our door frame is wide.
It is 20 plus 20.
That is 40 mm.
We can add a little wider on the right side.
You can also add 20.
We can set the position.
Right-click on this line.
Find the division at the top.
The division.
Here.
We can set our distance to the left end.
That is, the height of the yellow line below.
This line.
Its distance is 20.
Just now.
On this bottom plate.
We set a wider door frame.
That is, 20 mm wider to the right.
Then, after this point is set.
We will draw a vertical vertical line again.
Here.
On the right side.
We found the internal multi-sided line tool.
The shortcut key is G.
Then press.
Start.
Press the Shift key.
It will draw a vertical line.
Then on the top position.
Double click.
End.
OK.
After the drawing is done.
We use this edition.
The tool.
On this section.
Right key.
Cut and sew.
OK.
Then we.
This door frame.
From the touchpad.
We can see that this.
Is the touchpad.
It is the top.
This is the top.
This is the bottom.
The width of the door frame has been changed.
After the change, we will do the upper and lower segment of the panel.
The front panel has a hollow line in the middle, as you can see.
This can be cut and sewn directly with the hook and loop tool.
For the door frame, we need to manually draw a horizontal inner line.
We will use the inner multi-line tool to draw it.
Start with the left button, and end with the left button.
Because there is a small hollow line on the left, we know that it is drawn here.
Use the hook and loop tool to select the two lines together, and then right-click.
The hook and loop tool, because we have the base line and the inner line,
so we use the hook and loop tool.
We can select all of them.
Then cut and sew again.
After the division is done, we will put the front panel on the right side of the screen.
The division line on it is not very smooth now.
We can use the tool to edit the curve to adjust it to be smooth.
First, we can use this edit panel tool to turn this time point into a curve point and remove it.
Then we can use the tool to edit the curve.
Or you can use the tool to edit the curve point.
You can try it.
Now I'm using the edit panel.
If I go to edit the edit panel, the whole line will follow the movement to adjust its curve.
Then we can also use the edit curve point to control the position of this curve point more accurately.
There are more here. I can delete a little curve point.
The curve points are the same, like here.
This is a curve point with a heading of left to right clockwise.
It is the same as a curve point with a heading of right to right clockwise.
You can see this.
Now I will adjust the curve point to the right.
I will do this.
Then this will be like this when the strength of the curve is equal.
The curve point is also aligned to the line jagged.
Well, that's basically it.
Then now the warping relationship is normal.
We can model with the control key.
Then take a look again.
Next, let's make a division of the big panel below the front panel.
It has two vertical dividing lines up and down,
and it also has a pocket and a belt cover.
Let's do it first.
Here, you can follow me
to operate the set value.
Here, we first find the plus point dividing tool.
The shortcut key is X.
Right-click on the line below.
Then, in the list of the
set, we input 65 on the left.
Then click again on the right.
Then the second paragraph is 25.
This is the range below me.
Then this line above should be right-clicked again.
We enter 30 in the first paragraph.
Then we enter 90 in the second paragraph.
Then based on the two division of this line above and below,
we can draw two vertical lines.
You can use the built-in multilayer line tool to start the single machine,
then the end point of the following double machine.
Then the single machine begins and the double machine ends.
The two dividing lines are then drawn.
After drawing,
we want to draw a pocket version based on this.
Then the pocket version will be a little wider than these two vertical lines.
Then based on this vertical line,
we first roughly set the position of our pocket.
Here, we still use this plus point dividing tool.
The shortcut key is X.
Then right-click on the dividing line.
Here, we can input 125.
It's about the height of our pocket,
or the length of its side.
Then,
we use the editing board tool to select the narrow line of these two divisions.
Right-click on the internal line diameter.
Because our pocket is going to be a little wider,
so I want to make the internal line diameter a little wider.
But now,
if I directly expand the two together,
it's all the same.
It's all facing left or right together.
So now,
I'm going to cancel it.
I'm going to do it one by one.
First, this one on the left.
Then right-click on the internal line diameter.
The diameter can be set to 10.
Then we don't extend it out.
The choice is not to extend it.
Then these two sides are out.
After a centimeter,
then we still need to check it again.
Check if these two lines,
the ends on the top,
are they connected to the outer edge of our board.
Because in a while,
our pocket is going to come out.
So it needs to be a closed shape.
So in order to make sure it's closed,
we can select both ends directly.
Press Shift to select both.
Then right-click,
add points to the outer edge of the board.
Add points to the outer edge of the board.
In this way,
our pocket,
at least on the top,
is closed.
We'll hook it up later.
And then what's left is
there's a middle point
of this shape.
Make it complete.
Then the middle point,
its position,
we can set it to
based on these two lines.
As a reference,
the middle line of them
is the point of the point
below the pocket.
On the middle line in the middle,
we can right-click on these two lines.
Between the lines,
create an inner line.
Create a middle line.
Then click OK.
You can also align this middle line
to the outside of the board.
Okay, based on this,
we can go to
make this pocket complete.
Okay, after it's done,
if you want to adjust its position again,
just use the edit board tool
to adjust the position of these points.
In addition,
in 3D,
now my base line,
the inner line is hidden.
You can display the inner line.
In this way,
you can see
the shape and position
of the inner line
on this clothes,
that is,
your pocket.
Now it will be made out of
what it looks like.
Then here,
I'll put the two sides of this,
the one just attached,
the two parts of this,
this line.
The two empty points are combined.
Then we can also pull out
this pocket a little bit,
just a little bit wider below.
When pulling,
you can go out
along the line itself.
Just go out along the line itself.
You can press the control key
and this kind of curve will appear.
Just a
elliptical number that goes out along the direction itself.
Then I am right-handed.
It extends out 10 mm,
which is one centimeter.
Then both sides are one millimeter.
and then both sides are the same.
In this way, the pocket is finished.
Next, let's make the cover.
The same operation is quickly completed here.
Here, I used the plus point division tool on both sides
to make a 30mm diameter
and a 20mm diameter.
Then, I used the plus point division tool
to make the inner lining,
because the cover is wider than the pocket.
I made an inner lining,
and the lining here can be set to 5.
The other side is the same.
This method is similar to the previous pocket.
To ensure that the top is closed,
we can let it align with the right arrow on the outer lining.
Here, choose the right arrow to align and add points to the outer lining.
Then continue to make the cover.
After making the inner lining on both sides,
join the right arrow.
It will become a complete line.
It is a kind of solid line.
The solid red circle.
In this way, we have already made the shape of the pocket and the cover on the front.
We can use the looping tool to make the panel.
The shortcut key is I to hook the looping tool.
Here, I will make the top, bottom, left, and right of the cover.
Make the panel frame.
Make the panel frame of this pattern.
Then right click and hook it as a panel.
Click on the blank area again.
This panel will come out.
In the same way, we will also hook the pocket for it.
The upper, lower, and lower lines must be selected.
Then right click on the selected line.
Hook it as a panel.
You can alwayspick it for lower or upper pages.
That's it.
Now the available lines can be deleted.
You can also delete the lines for the top panel.
And delete the minus lines too.
Remove the prove points too.
List it isolated.
And now we wish you have full commission.
That's okay.
The top one is also good.
Then after the board is hooked up, we can sew it together first.
Here you can use the free sewing tool to directly sew the pocket and the inner line on the large body of the inner line and then sew the belt cover.
If you want to sew the bottom line, you can't open the pocket here, so you can sew it to the upper line of the jacuzzi.
So here we use the editing board tool to see where we want to sew, because there is no specific start and end point on it.
Let's look for it first.
You can see that on the bottom board,
the belt cover
on the left side is 15.
Then on the top, we can also make a point of 15.
Selection on the right on the line.
Then set it to 15.
Then here, if we sew it, we also have to sew the belt cover first.
This line above, then the direction is set on the left, then we will go from left to right.
Start the button, end the button, and then the bottom is also from left to right.
Then because it is free sewing, it will have an equal point.
In this way, we know where it ends.
In this way, the belt cover is sewn.
The pocket and the belt cover are all sewn.
In 3D, we can add the pocket right click to the inside, and the belt cover right click to the side.
Add to the side.
Then you can pull it out a little bit, so that it will not be unstable when it is molded when it is molded.
Now we have sewn the pocket belt cover to it.
Then this, it itself has a sewing relationship between the top and bottom panels.
In fact, it means that our pocket has not been opened yet.
There is no way to open it.
It is actually in a state of sewing death.
Then we continue to modify here.
We can put this pocket first.
This pocket is inside.
The outside is a large panel.
We can separate it first.
Because we just drew two separation lines, and they are not separated yet.
We can use the edit panel tool.
Select these two lines together by pressing the Shift key.
Right click, cut and sew.
Then we will separate these two lines.
Then, the sewing relationship above, we will delete it.
In this way, our big body, it is in a state that can be opened.
Then in the opening state, we can also
move this opening part down a little bit.
In this way, we can probably see its opening position when we open it first.
Here, we can directly change it in 2D.
I can move this small piece of middle directly down a little bit.
Or we can directly press ESC to exit here.
Right-click on this line.
Inner line border.
Then here, we can input
and cut it off a little bit.
Then how much we cut off, you can do it according to your own design.
Then I cut about one centimeter here.
Then click OK.
Then right-click on this line and then cut it off.
Then we don't need this extra small panel.
Then you can see that in 3D now,
the design of our pocket is finished.
Then I can re-monitor it.
Let this pocket be restored.
Okay.
And on both sides, because I just cut off a section,
there should be no seam on both sides.
There is a small seam on the top.
There is no problem with the seam line.
Then we can simulate it by pressing the control key.
Okay.
The left side is also the same operation.
I deleted the panel that I just cut off on the left side.
Then we are done on one side.
Then on the other side, you can cut the panel.
I chose these two panels together.
I used the shortcut key to control plus D.
Then I gave it a copy-and-paste.
Then in 3D,
right-click on the pocket and add it to the inside.
Just move the lid slightly out a little bit.
Then simulate it.
Okay.
Now our pocket is ready.
The structure has been changed.
Next, let's add the button and the eye.
When adding the button and the eye here,
there are some details that need to be noticed.
Because we didn't set the position on this big body in advance,
so if we add it now,
we need to make sure that on the lid
and on the shape of the lid of the big body,
our position is relatively consistent.
Here,
we can choose to use the same reference
to add the button and the eye on the big body.
Then here,
we can see that they all have the following two lines.
We can use the following line as reference.
Here, we use the button and the eye tool.
I'm on this line below,
this line on the right side.
It's bright now.
I'm right-clicking,
and then I made a line in the eye
to create the button and the eye of the button and the eye.
Then here,
after right-clicking,
we will set the distance and interval
of the starting position
to the distance and interval of the starting position
in the window.
The distance here has been changed to 15.
You can also look at the following data.
Its 15 is the parallel distance of my button
and the selected yellow high beam line below.
Then the interval is the value on the left side.
Here, I changed it to 35.
Or 32.
32 is a bit appropriate.
Then click OK.
The above is also the same operation.
We still choose the same line.
Right-click on the same line.
Then change to the same value.
25, 32.
Then click OK.
Okay, the button and the eye.
These two,
now I have both buttons and eyes.
Because I'm using the same tool.
Then I can turn the button and the eye
right-click to the eye.
The conversion is to use this
while choosing the button and the eye tool.
Select the button and the eye tool.
Then,
in the selection,
this button and the eye
changed its direction.
Then use the button and the eye tool
to merge them together.
Now one side is done.
On the other side,
we can use this
select the button and the eye tool
to select the button and the eye frame
on the right side of our screen.
Then right-click
and directly copy to the
version of the symmetrical modification.
Just like our left side.
You can see it has been completely
symmetrical.
Then we simulate
and update the 3D model.
Okay, now basically
we have this style
modified.
Then we can hide
these basic lines
or those with internal lines.
Then next,
we will do some details
to make it perfect.
Mainly,
we can make it symmetrical
and double-layer performance.
Here,
I will put,
for example,
the cover,
we can right-click
and click the layer.
This version of the
The other parts are the same.
If it is a double-layer part,
you can do this.
You can go to,
for example,
the door,
select all the door panels,
then right-click
and choose this
one.
Then on the right,
by the way,
open it,
make it symmetrical,
make it symmetrical.
Then there are also
double-layer structures.
There is Shokufu,
then Xia Baiwei,
and also the collar.
Here,
we all use
this tool
of the colon layer.
You can directly colonize
a layer,
and they are automatically
sewed together.
Note that
if you
colonize
this collar,
remember our internal line,
it is also automatically
sewed together.
But,
we here,
this
this this
this is
also
this
is
And then read these information
Then it's convenient for us to choose the right fabric
So for non-downloaded fabrics
We can see its shrink chart
You can be on the left side
If you can hook it, you haven't downloaded it yet
I can hook it up
Then click the download button in the upper right corner
Then download it and have a look
You can also use it directly like this
You can take a look at these ingredients
To choose the appropriate fabric you want
For example, I chose a 2 here
The back is the fabric of 2
Then after changing the fabric
We remember to remodel it
Because the physical properties of this fabric are also different
After changing and applying the fabric
Then we will change its posture
Just like this
Change to a straight posture
Then you can also simulate it after changing the posture
Now that we have applied this fabric
Let's do it again
For its water-washing effect
The production of water-washing
Then first
Before we wash the water
Let's first confirm the color of our fabric
Because now we are using the fabric in the dustbin
Then it is wearing gray
But if we want
The color of the fabric is not this
Then we can change the color of this fabric first
Change the color
Is to choose this fabric
Then
The material window selects this piece of fabric
Then on the right side of the attribute editor
The texture of the fabric is found below the replacement
Then click on the color block
Then give it a new one
Everyone
Like the color you want
Then after changing the color
We are based on
What we want now
This piece of jeans
The appearance
Then follow him to do a water wash
Then we are going to use it here
Is our
A new feature of our
Ah
Um
There will be a selection of water-washing supply type below.
The default is the state of un-water-washed.
It is the original color of the牛仔 cloth that has not been water-washed.
It's just that we used the texture sticker and then we changed the color.
Then click on the download menu.
Take a look at some of the previews here.
There are universal washing, speed washing, stone washing, and so on.
Here, I can take you to make a switch.
You can have a little idea of ​​each water-washing effect separately.
Have a little impression
First of all, it's a plain wash.
This is a more basic water-washing supply type.
It can evenly color and soften the fabric.
At the same time, it is also the original color of the牛仔 to the maximum extent.
Then we changed the corresponding one to this one.
For example, after the plain wash type, we can also see some options below that can be set.
That is to say, the water-washing effect now.
We can go through the following, for example, softening.
The value of the water-washing, the degree of integration, the absorption, the duration, etc.
To adjust the overall effect.
And now this is a predetermined value.
Then let's take a look again.
There is also a speed wash.
The speed wash.
It's mainly through a slight fade.
The softening of the fabric presents an old-fashioned effect.
Then you can see that we have different types of crafts.
The following options are also different.
Then the speed wash corresponding to the following can be set to the concentration of the speed wash.
Then there is also the stone touch wash.
Then the stone touch wash is mainly in the process of washing.
The simulation of the kind of addition and absorption of friction fabric.
And then the effect of presenting natural wear and tear.
And then the corresponding one below.
It can adjust the color deviation intensity.
Then there is the acid wash.
The acid wash.
Then it looks like the visual effect is relatively clear.
It is through simulation.
After special chemical processing.
Form a strong contrast.
A large and thin pattern.
Then you can adjust the acid concentration of the acid wash below.
The following is the flushing.
The flushing is mainly done using the flushing technique.
To make the color change.
Based on the intensity of the processing.
It can present from a slight color change.
To the effect of almost white multi-layered.
The last is the smell wash.
The smell wash can achieve the natural restoration effect of the overall uniform color.
Make the jeans present the same light color.
So after you've done these predictions.
We pick a few.
Pick two.
I can give you a detailed introduction.
The following options.
Function.
First of all.
Here I have changed to a flushing.
You can see the effect in 3D.
And then because.
I want to do one.
Because now the whole body is this flushing.
I want to do a gluing effect.
So I can copy the current fabric first.
And then in 2D.
I go to the frame.
I want to do the flushing.
This version of the different parts.
Here I want to do.
The pocket.
The collar.
And then the bottom.
The door.
And then the jade.
And then these parts.
All selected.
And then on the right.
Find this new piece of fabric.
Copy this piece of fabric.
I can.
We can drag on the right.
The new piece of fabric of the object window.
Drag.
Drag it to the 2D.
On the board.
Or 3D.
On the selected board.
All right.
Then apply it to him.
And then here.
We can also select this fabric again.
You can judge.
Which half used it.
Because they are the same now.
So.
There is no difference in 3D.
And then the corresponding.
These two.
The two boards in the middle.
Also apply it.
Also apply it to him.
The second kind of fabric.
Ok.
Now that you have done the division of the fabric.
We first.
First adjust the first piece of fabric.
The first piece we just did.
Ah.
The first piece of this fabric was selected by the object window.
Just doing it.
It's select it.
Is the working type of sliding wash.
Then below.
You can see it.
There will be a water wash picture option.
If you don't see it.
Just point the small triangle next to it.
Can open it.
Can see.
Below.
There will be a water wash picture.
The water wash picture.
This side.
Is the water wash picture.
There are.
There are the three colors.
The three colors.
For example, this is the water-washing pattern used for the current water-washing effect.
It is based on this effect to carry out the whole water-washing effect.
Then click on the small triangle next to it.
Click on the small triangle next to it and you can see that there are some conversion options below.
You can adjust the angle of this pattern and then the width and height.
For example, if you think that the pattern is too small and the pattern is too small, you can enlarge it or shrink it.
Then go down and select the color-canceling intensity.
You can adjust it to see the effect.
The color-canceling intensity of the smothie here is controlled by the degree to which we wash out the white area.
The larger the value, you can see that the color-canceling intensity of this clothes
is on the fabric.
The lighter the color, the more obvious it is.
Then the following conversion option is now default to fold.
This is the same as some of the patterned conversion modes in our PS.
There is soft light, front and back, and so on.
Here we can generally keep the default option of folding.
If you need, you can try other folding methods.
You can do different design effects.
Then go down and select the color-canceling intensity.
The color-canceling intensity is controlled by the effect of the water-washed pattern.
It is the degree of blurring between the deep and the shallow.
Now I have changed the color-canceling intensity to 31, which is enlarged.
The larger the color-canceling intensity, the larger the degree of blurring it is.
Because now these two pieces of fabric are the same.
At the beginning, it is the same.
I will change this part above.
You can see the difference in contrast between them.
Then the duration of the center is that the longer the water-washing time,
it will be whiter overall.
Then there is a fold-on friction at the end.
The last fold-on friction is when we applied the cow's body to the fabric on the fabric.
That's when the effect will appear.
So this is what we do.
I will introduce it to you later.
After understanding these parameters, we will make a general adjustment.
The color-canceling intensity is changed to 40.
The absorption is changed to 8.
Then the duration is changed to 35.
In this way, the first piece of cow's body fabric is adjusted.
Then the second piece is changed.
The second piece is the fabric of this fold-on.
Then we can change the water-washing supply type to it.
You can make a different water-washing type of this fold-on design.
There is a rinsing.
Or just used acid washing and rinsing.
We can use the effect of this rinsing here.
Then the same is also corresponding to the water-washing pattern below.
Then the rinsing below corresponds to the density of the rinsing.
The same if the value is larger.
In fact, the white area is the water-washing.
The more obvious.
Here we go directly to modify.
Change to 80.
Then the absorption.
It can be changed to a little bigger.
Change to 20.
Then the duration of the cycle.
We can try to change to 52.
It's too white.
We change to 35.
Then the adjustment here is to make the two fabrics of this fold-on.
It's more natural and harmonious.
Okay, now you can see the 3D window.
Our fabric of this fold-on.
The water-washing effect of the fabric is already set.
Okay, next.
We're going to do some detailed design on it.
Because it's not so real to look at the whole thing now.
We are in the production of the dress.
Its side and some of the edges.
It will have some different water-washing effects.
So here we are going to add some water-washing details.
Let's take this door frame as an example.
Here we are going to use an object window.
A seamstress tool.
We use the seamstress tool to simulate.
For example, the right side of the door frame.
Here to press two double stitches.
Just two lines.
Double stitch line.
And then a water-washing effect on it.
So here we can open the door frame window first.
In our material this time.
Find it in our live material.
You can see that there are two water-washing materials on this side.
One is pinyon water-washing.
One is border water-washing material.
First of all, we see this pinyon water-washing.
And it's a PNG sticker.
Picture.
Then we drag it directly to the right side.
Because I have selected a default pinyon on the right side.
So it will appear below.
The properties corresponding to the pinyon.
Then it will have its textual picture position.
Now it's empty.
We drag this pinyon water-washing picture over.
Then the following發現 picture is different.
We can delete and recreate one.
In this way, in fact, our pinyon water-washing.
Its water-washing effect.
Is to use our.
The picture provided to you.
This picture has been completed.
Self-defined pinyon water-washing.
Then we use this pinyon water-washing.
Use.
Line pinyon water-washing.
Or free pinyon water-washing tools.
You can add it to the door frame.
You can take a look at the effect in 3D.
After adding in.
Now it.
We can adjust it again.
According to the 3D visual effect.
This pinyon water-washing.
Its specifications.
Mainly.
Right side of the object window.
Select this pinyon water-washing.
In the following.
In the attribute editor.
Find its specifications.
You can modify its width.
Width narrow.
Because the door frame is wider.
This change is wider.
It will look better.
Then modify its density.
You can make it.
Not so tight.
This side is changed to 110.
OK.
The door frame is added here.
Then.
The same operation.
We can.
The rest.
Other parts.
The same.
Double needle.
Press line.
The effect of this pinyon water-washing.
Add it to it.
Then.
For example.
This sleeve.
This circle.
Then.
There is.
The pinyon.
Then.
In front.
The front.
These pinyons.
Then.
The back pinyon.
Can be added.
Then.
In front.
This big body.
Our.
The pinyon.
This pinyon.
It may.
The main body.
The door frame is wider.
But.
In front.
We want to make a narrower one.
That is.
Narrow double needle pressure line.
Then.
We are here.
The corresponding pinyon.
The pinyon is also smaller.
I copied it out.
Then.
The specifications below.
Changed to 15.
That is.
Narrow.
Then.
Use.
Free pinyon.
Pinyon tool.
In this way.
Is
Next add the key.
Then.
Add to our.
Cover.
After adding, we again add.
Because the fact that.
We just said.
We have double needles.
Tutorial for me.
Come on up.
In fact, I am in.
So let's add the line of sight again, because here I am using visual design, that is, I added this learning effect to show you, but in fact, if we have a process unit and then we have a double needle in a certain part, for example, it is a 1mm plus 6mm, such a specification has been set up, then it is recommended that everyone should add the line of sight first, and then add the appropriate
folding fold effect according to the specific specification of the line of sight you added, and then add the appropriate folding fold effect to the corresponding line of sight.
This way, the width of the folding fold can be set according to the line of sight, and then I will add the line of sight here
or take the force of the door in this place as an example. Here, I first used the default line of sight in the object window,
It's still relatively shallow, I can't see it too clearly.
We can adjust its specifications in the lower right corner of the mouse.
You can make it a little thicker.
And then change its color.
After the single needle is set, we come to the bottom.
There is an environment setting at the bottom.
We change the number of environment settings to 2.
And then the diameter can be changed a little bigger.
Because now my water-washing effect is relatively wide.
It's the same principle.
If you have the corresponding specifications of the supply unit,
you can just enter the corresponding specifications directly.
Okay, so I've changed the width of this line.
And then, just like adding the wrinkle curse just now,
we can quickly change the remaining parts
that need to be changed.
All the parts that need to be added to the line are added.
And then, in the narrow part,
a narrow wrinkle curse has just been copied.
Now I copy the line again.
And then its width is also changed to narrow.
Then add
the width of the wrinkle curse.
And then the width of the cover.
Okay, so now I've just been using the water-washing effect of the wrinkle curse.
If you don't have time to follow the chain,
you can just use this effect to add it gradually.
And then we continue to do it.
And then next,
we also provide another water-washing material,
the edge water-washing.
We can add it to the edge of the door,
the edge of the door,
the edge of the collar,
and some of the places of the bottom.
Now our water-washing material
is a TPT format.
It's a water-washing curse that we,
Clo, have brought.
This is a way of saving water-washing.
If you want to save it,
like the pre-setting of the wrinkle curse we just made,
the settings we've done,
we can select it.
And then in the lower right corner of the first line,
the first line of the attribute editor,
there will be a save button.
If you save,
it's saving such a TPT format.
So for this kind of preview,
you can drag it directly into the physical window.
You can drag it in directly and use it.
After dragging it in, it can be used directly.
We use this free sewing fold or thread sewing fold tool.
Then we can add it to the collar.
Then you can also add it to the collar.
Now it's still a little bit different.
But now it's not very obvious.
Let's add it to the collar.
Okay, now the collar is added.
But it's not very obvious.
Now we need to use the last option when we were just doing the cowhide study preset.
Okay, now we need to use the cowhide study preset.
Let's go back to the material in the material window.
Then select any one of the materials.
Let's select one of the materials first.
I chose the second one.
Because I just added it to the second piece of material.
Then below.
The bottom one is the last option of the cowhide study preset.
There is a seam allowance.
What it controls is the degree of deepness of the furring added to the fabric.
So we can change the number a little bit.
For example, change it to 55.
Now we can clearly see the fabric of the 3D window.
It just added the furring pleating part.
Its edge is water-washed.
This pleating effect.
Okay, so add it like this.
We can see it in other places.
Where else do you need to add such a pleating effect?
Make it look more real overall.
Make it look fuller.
For example, the seam allowance of our bottom.
Here, it provides you with two of these water-washed effects.
So if you have food reference.
Then you want to extract the furring on the food.
If you want to extract the water-washed effect of the furring.
You can refer to our.
It's also on Bilibili.
The previous live class.
It's also a cowhide.
But it's a cowhide special in the direct car topic.
There is a detailed explanation in the live class.
How to extract from food.
Extract such material.
Okay, here.
I'll copy it out.
It's the water-washed edge.
We can also have wide and narrow.
Then on the bottom.
And on the jade.
To add a wider water-washed effect.
Then on the bottom and on the shauker.
Our
The curse is.
One.
We just talked about two.
One is just directly.
By default.
Just directly put our curse.
and drag it directly to the position of the pattern.
One is the pattern of the PTP that we have already set.
And then we can add a little more to the corresponding pocket.
Because the pocket is a little protruding on the inside,
we can also add a little bit of the effect of this negative fold.
In addition, on the inner line,
if you add a negative fold on the inner line,
we have added it now.
And then if you can hear it on the outside,
you may hear it on the outside,
you will have a flip on the right position.
Let it flip over.
Then I can check it again.
Basically, we have some of the water-cleaning effects of this jacket,
the cowboy jacket,
and the negative fold.
It's also set up.
Then, overall, we can put this
button to change it into a metal button.
Then the color of the button eye can also be changed to the same.
Now we have two buttons in the object window.
Two types.
It means that we may have just added it when we added it.
Added them to different types.
Now I can use this to choose the moving button tool.
Take it all out.
On the right, we are in one of them.
Click the download button on the right side of a certain button.
It is to apply the same button to them.
The same operation.
Choose again.
There is a button eye.
Then come to the object window button eye this row.
We can be on the right side.
We want the button eye on the right side.
Click on this application button.
That is, the same one on the application.
Select the same one on the application.
The same button eye.
In this way, it is convenient for us to unify their color and material.
The color of the button eye.
Here you can.
I'm opening the color window now.
But we can also switch to the name line this row.
You can choose any name line.
Because we set a color to the name line.
We can change it to the same color.
Because there is no record.
We can go back to the name line this row directly.
Then.
Select the color of the name line.
Add it to our color board.
In this way, I will go back to the button eye this row.
I can apply this color.
Then the button button.
Now this button button.
We can change it to a.
The surface is flat and smooth.
That kind of metal button button.
Here we can first change its shape preset.
This is some of the presets in our library.
You can choose according to the need.
Then change its material type to metal.
What about metal preset?
There are some metal preset colors below.
Then we can choose according to the need.
For example, retro copper.
Or silver.
You can choose according to the need.
Okay.
Now.
After setting the parameters of the button button eye.
Finally.
We.
There is a small detail about this button button.
That is.
If we.
We can adjust the position of this button button.
Here.
I'm going to put the button button eye out first.
You can see the modification on my side.
Then you know.
What kind of effect we want to make.
Here.
I'm going to put it first.
I'm going to put the button eye out.
And then.
It's default now.
It's actually in the middle of the button eye.
It's in the middle of the button eye.
But in fact.
I want it to be a little bit to the left.
Just a little bit.
Because its phoenix eye.
It's to the left.
This button eye.
So.
I'm on the right here.
I changed the position of the button eye to 20.
And then.
Move this button eye to the right.
There's actually a green dot in the middle.
You can see it on your screen.
Maybe a little bit clearer.
Plus this dot.
This dot is our button.
It's actually in the center of the collection.
How about this?
After the adjustment.
We can see the changes in 3D.
That's our button eye.
It's going to stick out.
And then.
Our button is mainly written on the left.
And this is the green dot.
So.
Since we've adjusted our button eye.
And then.
There's one more thing we need to improve.
That is.
We're going to.
We're going to apply.
Polymer.
With the awesome glitter.
The purple color.
And then.
We're going to apply a little bit of the same color.
We're going to apply it.
with the same color.
With the same color.
And we're going to apply it.
It's a little bit.
But you you can see.
You can see.
The different colors.
And then.
Then here we can use a few water-washing materials from our library to see if we can use the materials in it directly in our library window
Then press the shortcut Y to open the library and press it again to close it
Then come to the fabric library and find the water-washing text file in it
There are some water-washing preset patterns in it
Here are some of the water-washing presets that we just left
And then the material picture of these effects
And then there are some water-washing effect pictures of these steps
For example, this is like a whole pair of pants
Its whole
The shape of the scratch
The effect is that it can be extracted from the food
What about this method of extraction?
You can go to our previous video
And here I choose one of the last 06
I'm here because it's downloaded
I'll just use it
Then right-click on it
You can apply it to our
Right-click to add as a sticker
For example, apply it to this sleeve
Then click OK
You can enlarge it a little bit
Now it's smaller
Then the corresponding 3D can also be turned to the corresponding angle
For example, put it on the elbow to show the white area of the neck
If I enlarge this sticker
And then our board is also parallel
You can choose a sticker in the middle
There is an option on the right side of the sticker
You can open it
In this way, between our boards
Its sticker is connected
It will be more convenient
Okay, now this
After adjusting the position of the sticker
We are on the right side of the object window
Select this sticker now
After selecting this sticker
Then below
First you can preset its effect
Change to mixed with fabric
Change this
Mainly I want it to be mixed with the fabric
Mixed with the fabric
Use the same發現 picture with the same fabric
Because I am now
Under the bottom of this
The pattern of the calf cloth
I hope it can
My sticker and this mechanism can be mixed better
Mix more realistically
So I have to choose to mix with the fabric
After choosing
Next, let's modify its opacity
Because it's too white now
Go straight down to opacity
Here you can change it to 20 or 10
You can change it according to the 3D effect
Then after changing
If you think this color
It will be a little gray
You can change the color of this sticker again
Make it blue
It's based on what we need
We want it to be washed out
After white is
Is it a little blue or what color
You can modify it here
Then this side is done well
After this side is done
On the other side
We can copy this sticker directly
Ctrl C Ctrl V
Put it in this position
The same
If you want it to connect at the intersection
You have to select the middle sticker
Open this at the intersection
Then we can also do the front
Is to show that some of the details
There will be some of this effect
You don't know if you can see it clearly on the screen
You can
If you don't see it clearly on your screen
You can adjust this value again
It's obvious
Okay, now our
This one
Jack
There is also a jacket
Basically, this style is finished
We can save it
Remember to save
Because we still have to do the matching display later
Let's save this version first
OK
After saving
Next
Yes
And then add a little
Because we are now
In fact, I mainly make it around the appearance
Let's say I'm going to do some opening
Or internal display
Or a single display
Then we will record the back of this fabric
Right
We will see
The back of this jeans
The back of the jeans
It's the fabric
It will be more shallow
The color is different
So at this time
We need to adjust it
The color of the back
Here I see below
I choose the fabric above first
Then
If we want to adjust the back
It's in the attribute editor
It has a positive and a negative side
This is the color setting of this fabric
So here we choose the back
Then here I don't have it
It's not hooked
It's the same as the front
Then the back is set separately
According to the current setting
We can change its cycle
Continuity
Time
Long
That is, the water wash time
Through this value
That is, the water wash time is long
It will be half white
This principle
So we change it
After changing
We 3D
Can present this kind of
The back will be a little lighter
This effect
Of course, if you still want
Some other effects
Just go to adjust
The parameters here
Just fine
The same operation
We can use these two pieces of fabric
The color of the back
To give it
The overall lightening
Treat it
Then after processing
For the two-layer structure
Like the bottom
The jade and the collar
These parts
It should be facing forward
From the inside
It's also the front fabric
We can right-click on the board
Turn over the surface
It's the same on the sleeve
Right-click on the board
Turn over the surface
It's the same on the collar
You can save it again
You can simulate it
Save again
Now we have this one
The production is complete
Then save it now
Okay, what's next
If we want to do a matching display
First of all, I want to
Give it
Change the posture
Because we recommend everyone
When doing matching
Don't stand upright
Like this
We may have that
If the amount is more
Where is the pile
It's not easy to go
When matching
It may be easy to wear
Not stable
It will take some time to adjust
So first of all
When we do
When wearing
We can put the posture first
Unified adjustment
A pose
Or open A pose
Here we
First find the male model posture
Here
I changed it to
A-shape posture
Because I provide it to everyone
The material is also A-shape
Then
In addition
My jacket jacket
The jacket jacket is worn outside
Is open
So I can put this first
Untie the button
Untie it
Use this
Still use the button button tool
Because it is
Open with the button button tool
Unite
Then
Still use this button button tool
Go to the frame
Can be untied
Go straight to the frame
Then simulate again
Wait for him to
Change
After changing the posture
We just
Go directly to the double machine
Change the posture
Change the position
After changing the posture
Now
Because of our button
It's open
But sometimes
It will be outside
Because the button and the board
There is a conflict
That is
There will be a collision between them
In order to prevent it
It's easy to be unstable
Need time to simulate
I just
These two front doors
Is
It's two of its layers
These two boards
Just move out a little
So simulate
It will be faster
Then you can
Let them separate a little
Adjust the position
On the left side
I just
On the pocket
This button button
The eye was untied by me
I remember it again
Click on the button button
Click on the button again
The eye can be untied
It might have been a frame just now
There are too many frames
Untie this side as well
Okay, now
After this version is finished
Everyone pay attention
Save
If you want to save
Don't put the original
The file just saved
Covered
Click on the file
Save as a project file
Then we will give it
Save one
This is the open version
it is good
After saving
Everyone can
You can open our picture library again
Here I am
Double-click
Opened our inside
This dresser file
Is a T-shirt
Wear a pair of pants
Because I have saved
I can open it directly
So
Everyone remember to save the file
Then I will directly double-click here
Open this dresser file double-click
After opening
The shortcut key is to turn off the picture library
Turn off
OK
Here
We will give you
Use this water-washing preset again
Because
In addition to
We can
On the fabric of jeans
Use this water-washing effect
But in fact
The style of our needle
For example, this kind of
Shirt
T-shirt
It will also have some
This kind of water-washing effect
This style
And if it is
Other types
For example, on the hat
We can also use this water-washing process
To make its surface
The effect of water-washing
Then everyone first
This file
Open
After opening
We first
To this shirt
Then do
The effect of water-washing
And this T-shirt
First
Still the first step
We first determine
The color of our water-washing
This cloth
Its color
Its original
I hope it is a
Water-washing
The color
But first
I hope it is a
Well, after the water is washed
It is a gray
Or gray
I will pick one first
A darker color
A gray
primo
And this
Darked
A little black
This color
And then
On the right
After selecting
After setting
Its material type
Change to
Single cloth
Then
Allow
you can also set it according to your needs.
Here I directly select the stone ink wash.
Then you can change its intensity below the corresponding one.
Dye intensity
You can change it a little bit.
It's just that the black and white contrast is not so obvious.
Then if you don't think the current water wash pattern is big enough,
you can go directly to the transition
to increase the percentage of the water wash pattern.
In this way, the water wash effect of my T-shirt is set.
You can also recall that if we are in everyday life
or when making some designs,
see what style it is,
it is also such a pattern or such a water wash effect.
You can set this process
and apply it to your clothes or fabric.
Next, before we import the jacket,
we do some preparation work first.
It is convenient to do the combination later.
Because the pants have no contact with the jacket,
we can double-click on the pants.
Double-click on the pants, select the pants,
then right-click to freeze,
and then press Ctrl A to full select.
On the right, we change its layer to negative one.
Then here I double-click the T-shirt again,
and change its shrink rate to 80%.
Just let it shrink.
Let it be a little tighter.
Change the shrink rate to 80 at the tail.
This is the horizontal direction.
Change it to 80.
Make it tighter.
It's convenient for me to wear this jacket.
Then we open the blouse.
After opening the blouse,
right-click to increase to the work area.
That is to add the jacket
that we just made to the open pattern.
Here I am adding.
Remember to add.
Don't replace the original file.
Then click to confirm.
Because you see that we all use the same posture,
it will be more convenient to do the combination.
In addition,
pay attention to me in these two files.
When the jacket and the jacket are stored,
we have not improved the quality before.
It is because when we are wearing it,
the computer's computing capacity will not be so large.
Otherwise,
its response will be slower.
After adding,
we can press the control key to simulate.
After the simulation is stable,
we will slowly change the shrink rate of this T-shirt inside.
Change to the normal size.
Now it is 100%.
We can directly change it to the green one inside.
The green one is the T-shirt.
Double click on the T-shirt.
Select the whole T-shirt.
Then on the right,
change the shrink rate to 90%.
Then simulate stability.
After the simulation is stable,
we double click again to change it back to 100%.
This is to prevent it from sticking out.
We are gradually changing it to the large size.
Change it back.
Here,
I can take this.
This is the jacket.
Hide.
Shift plus Q.
Select the sheet.
Shift plus Q is to hide.
Look inside.
It's all normal.
Then there is no problem.
Then,
Shift plus W is to display.
Display all the sheets again.
Because this is already worn.
So its layer can be changed to 0.
This T-shirt.
Double click all the sheets.
The layer on the right is changed to 0.
Shift plus W.
All the sheets.
Let's display this jacket back.
Then,
after there is no problem on the top,
we untie the pants.
The shortcut key is Shift plus K.
Double click on the pants.
That is to select all the sheets.
So all the sheets related to the pants are sewn together.
All selected.
Then Shift plus K is to untie.
Then,
again.
Change its layer to 0 on the right.
Shrink rate means that we have set the layer.
And now change it back to 0.
It will return to the default state.
Normal state.
Then the whole can be simulated again.
Then next.
Change it to an upright position.
So if you are the final display effect.
There are some other positions.
At this time,
you can go to the change of the position you want to show.
Because now there is no improved quality.
The speed of switching will also be faster.
Then,
after changing the posture,
simulate again.
Then,
improve quality again.
For improved quality,
we can directly use this improved quality tool.
Just according to the current setting.
Then click to confirm.
Then,
re-simulate again.
Because now.
It is a high quality state.
There are also more accessories.
You can simulate a little more.
Then you can see the final result.
Then,
we can now finish the whole set of outfits.
we can also do some matching,
match some accessories.
This is also in our material.
Then you can directly have a few documents prepared here.
Ears.
And this.
Glasses.
Then these materials,
you are.
is ZACS, which is the format that we have designated as a configuration.
You can directly double-click to load it in.
For materials like this, we can go to Connect Business City to download.
There are a lot of free resources.
And then in the format of this ZPAC,
everyone remembers that it is a clothing file format.
So if you put it in,
you need to right-click to add to the work area,
or when you drag it in,
you must choose to add it in this pop-up window,
because otherwise you will replace the original file when you reopen it.
So at this time, you must choose to add and then click OK.
This has been placed in the neck in advance,
so we basically put it on and don't have to adjust it.
Okay, so now the whole set of combinations is finished.
Finally,
based on the picture,
our reference poster is a view that looks to the side and a view that looks to the left.
I can also go and adjust it again with this tool that we use to adjust the joint point.
The shortcut key is Shift plus X,
and this kind of Google point will appear.
Then you go and adjust its head direction,
and then hide it after adjusting it.
Finally, we will add a background display to it.
In the library,
in the scene file folder,
you can use this one here.
You can also go to the business city to add other backgrounds.
Here we will directly use this one.
The background of the bunker,
right-click to add to the work area,
and then after adding it in,
there are some unnecessary materials that we can delete.
Then we can delete it.
Finally, this is basically done.
Then finally, we can enter a render.
Let's take a look at the effect.
Then open the render window here.
Then turn on powershell render.
For this rendering,
we can first set it,
and we can change it if we want.
And it will show the result after this process.
OK, it's ready.
We will use it in this scene.
the size, resolution, and lighting settings of the rendered picture, and so on.
So it's been a long time. I'm not going to continue to render here.
In addition, let me tell you again.
If we want to make it,
because now it's rendered and the window is white.
If you want to do the same as the reference picture,
if you want to make it out of the sky,
or if you have a natural environment,
you can do it in the lighting settings of the rendering.
I'll stop rendering here.
In the following point, find this light attribute.
In the light attribute,
there will be a skylight on the right side.
And then on the side of the environment,
we can put an HDR picture.
And then in our training for everyone,
there is an HDR file in this live material.
There are three downloaded HDR files in it.
You can use it directly.
I'll copy the path here first,
because I'm going to open it later.
Right click on the file and copy the path.
You can copy it to its location.
And then on the right side of the environment,
click on the plus sign on the right side.
And then on top of that,
I can paste my path in here,
and then go back to the corresponding position.
And then open it.
Oh, there are a few sky materials prepared here.
You can try it out.
So after adding it in,
you can go down and change the light intensity and the light angle.
If the light is relatively weak,
you can go back and fill in some orange lights,
and so on.
These different types of lights on the other right side.
So about rendering,
we also have a live class about rendering in the previous master direct car.
You can also go to that inside to see a specific live class.
OK, now the rendering time is relatively long.
This side is not rendering.
So you can actually see the preview.
There is already this environment in the back of the preview.
The sky environment is here.
You can adjust it again.
Thank you.